var questions = [
    {
        "question": "What is one difference between Java and JavaScript?",
        "options": ["They are different branches of the same programming language", "Java is an OOP programming language whilst JavaScript is an OOP scripting language", "Java code is written in the form of text whilst JavaScript needs to be compiled"],
        "answer": "Java is an OOP programming language whilst JavaScript is an OOP scripting language"

    },

    {
        "question": "Which of these is not a datatype supported by JavaScript?",
        "options": ["Boolean", "String", "Number", "Abbreviation", "Undefined"],
        "answer": "Abbreviation"
    },

    {
        "question": "Is JavaScript a case-sensitive language?",
        "options": ["Yes", "No"],
        "answer": "Yes"
    },

    {
        "question": "What is the purpose of an Attribute?",
        "options": ["It is the value assigned to the property such as; value=’Name’ etc", " It provides more details on an element like id, type, value etc"],
        "answer": "It provides more details on an element like id, type, value etc"
    },

    {
        "question": "Which is not a way to define a variable in JavaScript?", 
        "options": ["let", "var", "desc", "const"],
        "answer": "desc"
    },

    {
        "question": "What does === mean in JavaScript?",
        "options": ["Subtract", "It allows you to compare a number and a string as equals", "It compares both the value and variable"],
        "answer": "It compares both the value and variable"
    
    },

    {
        "question": "What does the ++ Increment mean in JavaScript?",
        "options": ["It adds two to the value", "It adds one to the value","It integrates C++ into the code"],
        "answer": "It adds one to the value"
    },

    {
        "question": "when is 'null' used in JavaScript?",
        "options": ["When a variable has been declared but has not yet been assigned a value", "When you would like to comment out a section of code", "It is an object that can be assigned to a variable as a representation of no value"],
        "answer": "It is an object that can be assigned to a variable as a representation of no value"
    },

    {
        "question": "Conditional keywords are:",
        "options": ["while", "for", "if", "until"],
        "answer": "if"
    },

    {
        "question": "What is a 'NaN' in JavaScript?",
        "options": ["Non analogue Number", "The garndparent of a child element", "Not a Number"],
        "answer": "Not a Number"
    }


]

